# ABDULKADİR SFMİZ

## Game Developer

\$\\ +90 531 259 01 90 @ abdulkadirsemiz@outlook.com https://github.com/greyhavvk

## **SUMMARY**

Hello! I'm Abdulkadir Semiz, a game developer, and a passionate gamer. I graduated from Istanbul University with a degree in Computer Engineering in 2021. I have gained experience in game development for over 2 years and have been involved in the development of games such as "Drop Weight" and "Smash Runner." Continuing to improve myself as a game developer, prioritizing professional ethics in my career, and always maintaining politeness are important principles for me. Feel free to reach out to me at abdulkadirsemiz@outlook.com to discuss potential collaborations or opportunities further. Thank you for considering my profile.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Game Developer-Intern

06/2021 - 08/2021

### **Tiplay Studio**

I have developed clones of six hyper-casual games.

- Cool Goal
- Johnny Trigger
- Bottle Flip
- Fun Race
- Count Master
- Traffic Racer
- Sky Roller

## Game Developer

2016 - 2017

### Morii Games

Manchester, UK

I have been working at Morii Games for 2 years. During this period, I was involved in the development of 20+ prototypes and a launch game called Smash Runner.

- Drop Weight
- Smash Runner

## **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of Computer Engineering

2016 - 2021

Istanbul University

Istanbul/Turkey

#### **PROJECTS**

#### Smash Runner

Date period

It is a project that I have been developing since its prototype at morii games. Thanks to this project, I experienced the process of working with more than one developer and going through a game until the launch stage. Teamwork and creating code standards among developers not only gave me experience from this project but also made me have fun.



## FIND ME ONLINE

- in Linkedin https://github.com/greyhavvk
- G Github https://github.com/greyhavvk
- Website https://greyhavvk.github.io

#### **LANGUAGES**

Turkish Native

English Advanced

## **SKILLS**

Unity · Game Development · C# ·

Zenject · OOP · Java · Github ·

SOLID · Mobile Games · C++

### **REFERENCES**

Sercan Gedik sercan@morii.games